techlomedia.in 2015-12-16

# Privacy Policy

At [Techlomedia.in](http://techlomedia.in/), we respect the privacy of our visitors. This privacy document outlines the types of information we collect at [Techlomedia.in](http://techlomedia.in/) and how we use that information:

### Log Files

Like many other websites, we also collect log files. This information include IP address, date/time, referring or exit pages, clicks, demographic information and click patter. But there is no information which is linked to any personal information of a visitor. There is nothing which can be used to personally identify a visitor.

### Subscribers

We collect emails of users who subscribe via feedburner. Feedburner is a third party service which automatically sends our feeds to subscribers email addresses. We do not share subscribers email with any other marketing company. We also do not use subscribers’ email to send promotional email. If a person does not want to receive emails, he can unsubscribe any time by using unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email sent by feedburner.

### Cookies

Techlomedia.in uses cookies to store information about visitor preferences. These cookies are used to server user-specific information when the user access the website again.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * We use Google ads and Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [Techlomedia.in](http://techlomedia.in/).
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [techlomedia.in](http://techlomedia.in/) and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

We also use some other third party ads which also use cookies similar to Google. All these cookies data are used to server user specific ads with matching interest. Techlomedia.in has no control or access to those cookies used by third-party advertisers. If you have any issue, you can consult to their privacy policies for detailed information. Techlomedia.in’s privacy policy does not apply to these third party advertisers.

If you wish to disable cookies, you can do it from your browser options. More information about the cookie management with specific browser can be found on the browser’s websites.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

###  [Deepanker Verma](http://techlomedia.in/author/admin/)

Deepanker Verma is a computer geek, web programmer and entrepreneur. He likes to write about technology gadgets and web security. 

__[http://techlomedia.in](http://techlomedia.in/)
